{"nodeID":23,"children":[{"nodeID":19,"children":[{"nodeID":18,"children":[{"nodeID":17,"children":[{"nodeID":4,"children":[{"nodeID":1,"children":[{"nodeID":0,"children":[],"question":null,"thisAnswer":"Analyze next Component","nodeType":"return","infoLink":null,"infoDesc":"return"}],"question":"This component is performing as expected. The defect is likely in a different component.","thisAnswer":"Yes","nodeType":"hypothesis","infoLink":null,"infoDesc":"All JSX Elements Drawn"},{"nodeID":3,"children":[{"nodeID":2,"children":[],"question":null,"thisAnswer":"Analyze next Component","nodeType":"return","infoLink":null,"infoDesc":"return"}],"question":"This component is performing as expected. The defect is likely in a different component. This component might have styling that prevents some elements from being rendered on screen. Please check the styling applied to verify.","thisAnswer":"No","nodeType":"hypothesis","infoLink":null,"infoDesc":"Likely Incorrect Styling"}],"question":"Are all JSX elements defined in this component being drawn on screen?","thisAnswer":"Yes","nodeType":"question","infoLink":null,"infoDesc":"Pure Component"},{"nodeID":16,"children":[{"nodeID":15,"children":[{"nodeID":6,"children":[{"nodeID":5,"children":[],"question":null,"thisAnswer":"Analyze next Component","nodeType":"return","infoLink":null,"infoDesc":"return"}],"question":"This component is performing as expected. The defect is likely in a different component.","thisAnswer":"Yes","nodeType":"hypothesis","infoLink":"","infoDesc":"Data in view is Accurate"},{"nodeID":14,"children":[{"nodeID":8,"children":[{"nodeID":7,"children":[],"question":null,"thisAnswer":"Analyze next Component","nodeType":"return","infoLink":null,"infoDesc":"return"}],"question":"In an impure functional component, state updates must be performed using React Hooks. (Learn more about correct usage of hooks)","thisAnswer":"No","nodeType":"hypothesis","infoLink":"","infoDesc":"State not updated using Hooks"},{"nodeID":13,"children":[{"nodeID":10,"children":[{"nodeID":9,"children":[],"question":null,"thisAnswer":"Analyze next Component","nodeType":"return","infoLink":null,"infoDesc":"return"}],"question":"This component is performing as expected. The defect is likely in a different component.","thisAnswer":"Yes","nodeType":"hypothesis","infoLink":"","infoDesc":"Correctly updated state with Hooks"},{"nodeID":12,"children":[{"nodeID":11,"children":[],"question":null,"thisAnswer":"Analyze next Component","nodeType":"return","infoLink":null,"infoDesc":"return"}],"question":"This component does not use React hooks as expected. Please create a copy of the state object and pass it to your created hook. ","thisAnswer":"No","nodeType":"hypothesis","infoLink":"https://reactjs.org/docs/hooks-rules.html","infoDesc":"Incorrectly updated state with Hooks"}],"question":"Are you creating a new copy of the existing state object, modifying it and passing it to the hook? (Learn more about correct usage of hooks)","thisAnswer":"Yes","nodeType":"question","infoLink":"","infoDesc":"State updated using Hooks"}],"question":"Is the state update performed using hooks?","thisAnswer":"No","nodeType":"question","infoLink":"","infoDesc":"Data in view is Not Accurate"}],"question":"Is the data or its behavior shown on the screen as expected?","thisAnswer":"Yes","nodeType":"question","infoLink":"","infoDesc":"All JSX Elements Drawn"}],"question":"Are all JSX elements defined in this component being drawn on screen?","thisAnswer":"No","nodeType":"question","infoLink":null,"infoDesc":"Impure Component"}],"question":"Is this component a pure component?","thisAnswer":"Function","nodeType":"question","infoLink":"https://medium.com/technofunnel/working-with-react-pure-components-166ded26ae48","infoDesc":"Component Type: Function"}],"question":"Is this component a function component or a class component?","thisAnswer":"Done","nodeType":"question","infoLink":"https://reactjs.org/docs/components-and-props.html#function-and-class-components","infoDesc":"Obtained Component List"}],"question":"Please enter all components where you suspect there may be a bug.","thisAnswer":"React","nodeType":"question: list components","infoLink":"https://reactjs.org/docs/components-and-props.html#function-and-class-components","infoDesc":"Framework used: React"},{"nodeID":20,"children":[],"question":"This is not supported yet","thisAnswer":"Angular","nodeType":"question","infoLink":null,"infoDesc":"Framework used: Angular"},{"nodeID":21,"children":[],"question":"This is not supported yet","thisAnswer":"Vue.js","nodeType":"question","infoLink":null,"infoDesc":"Framework used: Vue.js"},{"nodeID":22,"children":[],"question":"This is not supported yet","thisAnswer":"Gatsby.js","nodeType":"question","infoLink":null,"infoDesc":"Framework used: Gatsby.js"}],"question":"What framework or technology is being used?","thisAnswer":null,"nodeType":"question","infoLink":"https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Web_framework","infoDesc":null}